<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on thingsithinkithink</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/categories/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on thingsithinkithink</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thingsithinkithink.blog/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Jevons Paradox and the Kindle Web Proxy</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2026/02-09-jevons-paradox-and-the-kindle-web-proxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2026/02-09-jevons-paradox-and-the-kindle-web-proxy/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I have a Kindle Oasis that I&amp;rsquo;ve had for years and I love it. I really love reading, I feel good about myself when I read more, but I struggle to resist the allure of the internet and the ease of access that my phone gives me to a never-ending slot machine of interesting things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kindle Oasis has just enough connectivity built in to be useful. Long press a word and you can look it up in the dictionary or check Wikipedia. Occasionally I&amp;rsquo;d want to understand something from a book a bit better and I&amp;rsquo;d open the Kindle&amp;rsquo;s web browser to look it up. The browser used to be labelled &amp;ldquo;experimental&amp;rdquo; and while they&amp;rsquo;ve dropped that label, it&amp;rsquo;s still very bare-bones. Most modern websites render fine, albeit they don&amp;rsquo;t perform very well, but it&amp;rsquo;s not really been something that bothered me until recently.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Decade of Agents: Swyx's AI Engineer Paris Keynote</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/09-23-decade-of-agents-swyx-keynote/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/09-23-decade-of-agents-swyx-keynote/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="the-decade-of-agents-swyxs-ai-engineer-paris-keynote"&gt;The Decade of Agents: Swyx&amp;rsquo;s AI Engineer Paris Keynote&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At AI Engineer Paris, &lt;a href="https://swyx.io/aie-paris"&gt;Swyx (Shawn Wang)&lt;/a&gt; laid out his case for why we&amp;rsquo;re entering not just the year of AI agents, but an entire decade of agent-driven transformation from 2025 to 2035. His keynote updated his earlier AI World Fair talk with several converging trends that make this more than typical Silicon Valley optimism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to capture the things that stuck with me from the talk. These stood out:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Cogs / Interns / Human Tasks, a practical framework for AI transformation</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/05-05-cogs-intern-agents-and-human-tasks--a-practical-framework-for-ai-transformation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/05-05-cogs-intern-agents-and-human-tasks--a-practical-framework-for-ai-transformation/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;A while back, Drew Brunig&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href="https://www.dbreunig.com/2024/10/18/the-3-ai-use-cases-gods-interns-and-cogs.html"&gt;classification&lt;/a&gt; of AI capabilities as &amp;ldquo;Cogs, Interns, and Gods&amp;rdquo; went viral on &lt;a href="https://x.com/dbreunig/status/1847382010551292232?s=61"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;. I like it. It&amp;rsquo;s punchy. It&amp;rsquo;s powerful. I use it all the time, but I really dislike the Gods framing - even Brunig acknowledges these (superintelligent AI agents) don&amp;rsquo;t exist yet, so it&amp;rsquo;s really redundant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You basically can&amp;rsquo;t &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; anything with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also like Ethan Mollick&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href="https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/on-boarding-your-ai-intern"&gt;framework&lt;/a&gt; of &amp;ldquo;Automated&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Delegated&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;Just Me&amp;rdquo; as a way to talk about how we work with AI. But &amp;ldquo;Just Me&amp;rdquo; feels clumsy in professional contexts, and &amp;ldquo;Delegated&amp;rdquo; just doesn&amp;rsquo;t capture the dynamic back-and-forth relationship between humans and AI systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Synthesising a new framework for AI Transformation</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/05-04-synthesising-a-new-framework-for-ai-transformation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/05-04-synthesising-a-new-framework-for-ai-transformation/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Sparked by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/emollick_one-mistake-a-lot-of-companies-struggle-with-activity-7323721559481683969-j5Zm?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=member_desktop&amp;amp;rcm=ACoAAAKU3ZoBTHvzXgiOPqYTeQuTbQUqniMdk48"&gt;Ethan Mollick&amp;rsquo;s post about AI transformation&lt;/a&gt;, I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about how we frame AI&amp;rsquo;s role in workplace transformation. My current role involves doing this kind of work, and Ethan is correct to say we&amp;rsquo;re all figuring it out at the same time. Therefore, in that light, here are some things I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about lately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been considering two frameworks: &lt;a href="https://www.dbreunig.com/2024/10/18/the-3-ai-use-cases-gods-interns-and-cogs.html"&gt;Drew Brunig&amp;rsquo;s categorisation of AI use cases&lt;/a&gt; as &lt;strong&gt;Cogs, Interns,&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Gods&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/on-boarding-your-ai-intern"&gt;Ethan Mollick&amp;rsquo;s organisation of tasks&lt;/a&gt; into &lt;strong&gt;Automated, Delegated,&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Just-Me&lt;/strong&gt; categories.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The M×N Problem in Software Architecture</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/04-08-the-m-x-n-problem-in-software-architecture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/04-08-the-m-x-n-problem-in-software-architecture/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve heard about the &amp;ldquo;M×N problem&amp;rdquo; a couple of times lately. After watching Swyx on the Latent Space podcast interviewing the creators of MCP from Anthropic, where he mentioned this problem again, I decided to figure out what it actually meant. According to Swyx, it&amp;rsquo;s a problem he&amp;rsquo;s had to solve repeatedly in his career because of his work on developer tooling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="the-mn-problem-defined"&gt;The M×N Problem Defined&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The M×N problem occurs in software architecture when you have M components that need to interact with N other components, with each interaction handled individually. This creates a tangled web of connections where the total number of integrations grows to M × N.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Jackie Bavaro on Strategy</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/01-14-three-parts-of-strategy-with-jackie-bavaro/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/01-14-three-parts-of-strategy-with-jackie-bavaro/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Jackie Bavaro’s breakdown of strategy in her &lt;a href="https://www.lennysnewsletter.com/p/jackie-bavaro-on-how-to-build-product"&gt;recent podcast interview&lt;/a&gt; really stuck with me. She shared a simple (but I think, pretty good) framework that highlights three key components of strategy: &lt;strong&gt;Vision&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Strategic Framework&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Roadmap&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="1-vision-this-is-where-we-want-to-go"&gt;1. Vision: “This is where we want to go”&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vision is an inspiring picture of what the future looks like. Jackie framed it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Hey everyone, this is where we want to get to—don’t you want to build this future with me?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Three Ways I Think Frameworks are Good (actually)</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/250113-three-ways-i-think-frameworks-are-good-actually/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 09:20:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/250113-three-ways-i-think-frameworks-are-good-actually/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;A recent conversation with my friend &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jonathan-sykes-a702b4/"&gt;Dr Jon Sykes&lt;/a&gt; sparked some thoughts about where frameworks derive their value. The conversation started with a question: is the benefit of frameworks really just that they create a shared language? We were discussing my review of Chapter 2 of &amp;ldquo;How Big Things Get Done&amp;rdquo; and examining the framework that is emerging from my reading so far. This led us to identify three distinct sources of value in frameworks.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The challenges of mastering LLMs, and their role as cyborg enhancement</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/01-08-a-good-interview-with-simon-willison-on-around-the-prompt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/01-08-a-good-interview-with-simon-willison-on-around-the-prompt/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I recently watched a good &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rLcKbvmegag"&gt;interview&lt;/a&gt; with Simon Willison on Logan Kilpatrick&amp;rsquo;s podcast, hosted for Google. Simon is known for building &lt;a href="https://www.djangoproject.com/"&gt;Django&lt;/a&gt; (the Python web framework), &lt;a href="https://datasette.io/"&gt;Datasette&lt;/a&gt; (a data tool for journalists), and the &lt;a href="https://github.com/simonw/llm"&gt;LLM command line tool&lt;/a&gt; (which lets you run large language models from the command prompt). I used LLM for months until recently &lt;a href="https://www.answer.ai/posts/2024-12-05-introducing-shell-sage.html"&gt;Shell Sage&lt;/a&gt; became my daily tool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="takeaways"&gt;takeaways:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simon&amp;rsquo;s take that generative AI is best thought of today as a cyborg enhancement to our capabilities. I feel this way. These things make me so impactful and able to do what I already do, but better.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;However, he noted that these technologies don&amp;rsquo;t benefit everyone universally and threaten some livelihoods.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For instance, illustrators who rely on commissions may find their work threatened as individuals opt for generating assets using tools like Stable Diffusion or Flux.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simon&amp;rsquo;s take that LLMs are hard to master. Yes, most people have had an amazing experience that shows the power of LLMs, but it&amp;rsquo;s hard to get consistent high value results. And to do so, requires building a lot of intuition:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The notion that a powerful computer program, such as a large language model, cannot perform basic tasks like multiplication seems absurd to many.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;People have to build a mental model of LLMs, understanding their strengths and weaknesses, and recognising concepts like training cut-offs, hallucinations, and the probabilistic nature of outputs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One he didn&amp;rsquo;t mention but that I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about these days is around RAG systems. Users need to understand that even when LLMs are provided with legitimate sources, those sources compete with the model&amp;rsquo;s training data, which can introduce bias against the sources. The idea is totally foreign to most people. RAG doesn&amp;rsquo;t &lt;em&gt;fix&lt;/em&gt; anything - it has value - but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop the LLM saying something incorrect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some people think there is no longer any value to a computer science degree since LLMs can code.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But there is much more to creating great software than merely inputting a prompt and receiving functional code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legitimate uses of uncensored LLMs.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He shared an example of using Claude to extract campaign finance data from a report, where the AI declined to assist due to concerns about sharing personal financial information. This is absurd.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In another instance, a group analysing police body cam footage had to convince the LLM that dogs can bite people, as the model was biased towards pro-dog information based on its training data (the internet!).
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;and yet foundation model providers are understandably hesitant to share unfiltered models due to the (extremely high) likelihood that a news institution would (of course) publish scare articles about the LLM sharing unethical content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="thingsithinkithink"&gt;thingsithinkithink&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The thing about AI being a threat to many:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I feel this. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked a lot with artists, musicians, and writers. I &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; many of their clients would be perfectly happy with some AI &amp;lsquo;filler&amp;rsquo; assets and a lot of entry level positions in particular are at risk in these fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I hope people in these fields are able to use AI to amplify &lt;em&gt;their&lt;/em&gt; abilities to be more impactful too - but it&amp;rsquo;s definitely going to hurt folk. It makes me very self-conscious whenever I get excited about these things. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to overlook the negative impacts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;it does seem particularly unjust that rich silicon valley types train these tools on the work of the relatively underpaid creatives and the result is a massive threat to those already underempowered fields&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The thing about LLMs being hard to master:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I couldn&amp;rsquo;t agree more. I think there is a parallel between the examples he shares about individuals having challenges to master GenAI and the organisational challenges I&amp;rsquo;ve seen over the last couple of years.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The initial wave of generative AI adoption has produced impressive proof of concepts that often fail to evolve into viable products. This challenge arises partly from the technology stack (POCs are often built on independent systems that lack integration with organisational data pipelines etc).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;additionally though, a significant part of the issue specifically pertains to the challenge of mastering these tools. A POC shows what&amp;rsquo;s possible - but bringing a product to market that brings that value without causing a disaster in a multitude of edge cases is a much harder challenge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Is Psychology or Politics Behind Project Failures?</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/psychology-and-politics-behind-project-failures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/psychology-and-politics-behind-project-failures/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;A key theme from Chapter 2 of &lt;a href="https://amzn.eu/d/ifrzA2p"&gt;&amp;ldquo;How Big Things Get Done&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt; is that while we know we should think slowly and act fast, people often do the exact opposite. The chapter explores the psychological and political forces driving this behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="the-rush-to-commit"&gt;The Rush to Commit&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chapter introduces the concept of the commitment fallacy - a behavioural bias where we rush into decisions without proper consideration. The age-old advice &amp;ldquo;Act in haste, repent at leisure&amp;rdquo; captures this perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Does OpenAI's loss on ChatGPT Pro mean they're doomed?</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/01-06-does-openai-s-loss-on-chatgpt-pro-mean-they-re-doomed-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/01-06-does-openai-s-loss-on-chatgpt-pro-mean-they-re-doomed-/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;A WhatsApp group that I&amp;rsquo;m part of has been discussing whether or not OpenAI is overvalued and in trouble as a result of this recent &lt;a href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/01/05/openai-is-losing-money-on-its-pricey-chatgpt-pro-plan-ceo-sam-altman-says/"&gt;TechCrunch article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The key point here is that they believe OpenAI is targeting a traditional mass market product with this £200-a-month offering. Several individuals in the group argue similarly, viewing this as a traditional tech start-up with a product that costs a significant amount to run, raising questions about scalability versus costs. Some members of the group discuss adverts as the natural evolution of any scaling tech platform. One person states, &amp;ldquo;Every platform, when it moves from being a tool to an infrastructure for discovery, ends up running ads.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Think Slow, Act Fast: The Paradox of Project Planning</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/01-04-think-slow-act-fast-ch-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/01-04-think-slow-act-fast-ch-1/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;In the book &lt;em&gt;How Big Things Get Done&lt;/em&gt;, Bent Flyvbjerg and Dan Gardner presented an analysis of why large projects fail to meet their objectives. As someone who has witnessed the ups and downs of loads of projects, I&amp;rsquo;m very curious to learn what we can do better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the overarching themes of the first chapter is their thesis of &lt;strong&gt;“think slow, act fast.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="the-iron-law-of-megaprojects"&gt;The Iron Law of Megaprojects&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flyvbjerg and Gardner share what they term the &lt;strong&gt;“iron law of megaprojects,”&lt;/strong&gt; highlighting an uncomfortable reality: projects are consistently over budget, over time, and under deliver on benefits. It&amp;rsquo;s backed by an extensive database of over 16,000 projects across 136 countries and 20 different fields. The statistics are quite convincing:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Two AI things from Kent Hendricks' annual 'Things I learned' blog</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2024/12-30-two-ai-things-from-kent-hendrick-s-annual-things-i-learned-blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:16:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2024/12-30-two-ai-things-from-kent-hendrick-s-annual-things-i-learned-blog/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Two AI things I learned reading Kent Hendricks&amp;rsquo; annual &lt;a href="https://kenthendricks.com/52-things-i-learned-in-2024/"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Things I learned&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt; blog post:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The introduction of ChatGPT led to a 2% decrease in freelance job postings on Upwork.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While humans emit 27g of CO₂ when writing 300 words, ChatGPT accomplishes this in 4.4 seconds, producing only 2.2g of CO₂.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m relieved that using an LLM for grunt work doesn’t automatically force us to sacrifice caring about the climate. However, the notion of valuing people based on their carbon output feels dystopian ( like something out of Black Mirror).&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Off-the-Radar AI links for the End of the Year</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2024/off-the-radar-ai-links-for-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2024/off-the-radar-ai-links-for-2024/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Everyone has an exhaustive end of the year list. I don&amp;rsquo;t but there were a couple of things I got value from that I havne&amp;rsquo;t seen anyone else posting about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="the-civic-ai-observatory"&gt;The Civic AI Observatory&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://civicai.uk/?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_content=share"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civic AI Observatory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a community of civic-minded AI enthusiasts. It’s become one of my favourite spaces for fresh, thoughtful perspectives on AI. There are two reasons why I’m particularly glad I found this group:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Breadth of resources&lt;/strong&gt;: They share (and discuss) an incredible variety of articles, videos, and links on AI.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civic-first mindset&lt;/strong&gt;: Unlike many tech-focused spaces, their primary lens is civic impact, with AI as a means rather than an end. It&amp;rsquo;s not all positive discussion. The risks and downsides of AI on society are taken very seriously here and with a more grounded perspective than you usually find online.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This mix of perspectives cuts through the hype bubble dominating other feeds. I’ve found that their discussions and resources offer a higher diversity of angles compared to almost any other information source I follow.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Things I Think I Think</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2024/12-05-things-i-think-i-think-blog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:33:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2024/12-05-things-i-think-i-think-blog/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I want to use this blog to think, learn, and work in public..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I chose this name because I want to be able to write stuff without having to definitely commit forever to holding whatever ideas I have shared. Therefore these posts are just things I &lt;em&gt;think&lt;/em&gt; I think.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>