<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Product-Management on thingsithinkithink</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/categories/product-management/</link><description>Recent content in Product-Management on thingsithinkithink</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thingsithinkithink.blog/categories/product-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First Impressions of Claude Cowork Mode</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2026/01-13-claude-cowork-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2026/01-13-claude-cowork-first-impressions/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Anthropic recently released &lt;a href="https://claude.com/blog/cowork-research-preview"&gt;Cowork mode&lt;/a&gt; for Claude. It&amp;rsquo;s similar to Claude Code in that it&amp;rsquo;s highly agentic, has access to skills, and can make changes to files on your computer. But it has a nicer interface than Claude Code and is aimed at non-programmers, giving them access to the kind of general agent that all of us technical folk have been enjoying for a while now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You select a folder from your hard drive, give Claude a task, and it spins up a little virtual computer of its own that can read and edit those files. It&amp;rsquo;s allowed to browse the web, produce outputs, write its own code, and stuff like this.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Why we need Experiment-based Roadmaps in the AI Product Era</title><link>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/04-13-why-we-need-experiment-based-roadmaps-in-the-ai-product-era/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thingsithinkithink.blog/posts/2025/04-13-why-we-need-experiment-based-roadmaps-in-the-ai-product-era/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I recently &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R_HnI9oTv3c"&gt;watched&lt;/a&gt; a good talk by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/bryan-bischof/"&gt;Bryan Bischoff&lt;/a&gt;, Head of AI at Theory Ventures, on why traditional product roadmaps fail for AI development and how teams should approach building AI capabilities differently. The presentation provided a good mental model for shifting from rigid planning to experimental discovery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="the-problem-with-traditional-roadmaps-in-ai"&gt;The Problem with Traditional Roadmaps in AI&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traditional software roadmapping focuses on time estimates for when specific features will be ready for users. Product managers meticulously plan sprints, assign engineers to swim lanes, and establish checkpoints to track progress. When teams fall behind, they reassess, potentially cutting scope or adjusting timelines.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>